Hello! Little creatures of the Lord :V
How are you?
Today ehmm
YouTube sent me
One thing
Well I-I got it today, okay.
Eehh, I don't know what it is
But it looks like a gift, okay?
But it looks like a gift, okay!
Mangel come here, come here
Let's see this together, okay?
Mangel: Let's see Rubiuh, listen to me, emm... what is this?
Well, uh... something that YouTube sent me.
A: I have no idea.
M: Exclusively?
A: Exclusive? I think, I don't know, I don't think they sent this to anyone else.
M: Aa the parks...
R: Those fools
To Pewdiepie and those... bah!
R: He has my face, he has my face that...
M: Man no, no...
A: ...which is quite pretty
M: ...will have Cherra's face
A: elrubiusOMG, fully customized
R: Let's see.
M: I mean, on YouTube right now in the office, wait, it's amazing, huh?
A: It's embroidered, it has shine, look, look how it shines
M: It's like the Play, it's like the Play 4 Pro but...
A: It's like the Play 4 Pro but...
...but from YouTube
R: Well, let's- let's see what the hell it is.
R: A ver...
A: YouTube please...
A: *Rubius reads it*
Well, yes, don't tell me your life story...
M: Wow
R: Wtf
R: What the fuck is this, man?
R: *laughs*
A: A tracksuit, dude.
R: They look like the tracksuits that these Russians wear.
R: They dance in the street
R: Ohh
R: Look, it says my name
R: elrubius 2016
R: This is from Rewind...
M: That's outdated now, huh?
A: ...they gave it to me for that
R: Yes yes, it's a little outdated eh
M: Wait a minute, do you want to see something really fun?
A: What?
M: Do you want to see something fun Rubiuh?
A: Yes *laughs*
A: What?
M: *unintelligible words* So this is for the occasion, record me
R: Let's see *laughs*
R: What are you going to teach me, Mangel? I-I don't want to see you-
R: Ohh 17 son of a bitch
R: You're one size bigger than me.
M: ¡FIFITA!
Both: FIFITA! FIFITA!
A: It has been coincidental
M: Destiny
R: Fate unites us Mangel
M: Pokemon!
R: Yes?
M: Ooh!
A: I don't know, I mean
R: It fits me- It fits me well, doesn't it?
M: Clear man
M: The measure
A: With my name...
A: The measure...
M: What's up!?
A: I-I don't know
M: You're so crazy, eh, you're so crazy
R: What the hell happened here?
R: What the fuck?
M: It has possessed you!
M: You are possessed by the evil spirit
R: What the fuck is going on, man?
M: You carry the spirit of a Russian inside you
R: No, no
M: The spirit of...
R: D-don't touch it, don't touch it
M: ...by Dimitri
R: Mangel, stay away.
M: Dimitri's spirit!
A: The spirit of Dimitri
A: NO! DON'T TOUCH DIMITRI'S SPIRIT!
A: NO! NOOOO!
Fuck the chair :v
¡¡¡¡¡PARTY HAAARD!!!!!!!!!!
window...
Ust Moment~
A: God, thank goodness.
It was all a nightmare
NOOOO!
Help me D:
M: *Starts singing the US National Anthem*
M: How do I wear glasses while driving? I don't understand.
*doesn't say anything*
Here comes the police now
~SUBSCRIBE AND LIKE :D~
noninoninoninonino ni